I BROUGHT HIM
HERE.
OUR JOB IS
WITH DIMPLE.
DIMPLE!
WHO'S THAT?
I CAN'T DO
IT.
I CAN'T HANDLE
THESE 1 MILLION,
2.5 MILLION SETTLEMENTS.
JUST LEAVE!
SIR,
THAT GUY...
WHO'S THAT GUY?
A WORTHLESS GUY!
HE'S JUST WHAT
I SAY.
GO!
HE CALLS HIMSELF
A GUY!
NEXT!
MR.
DIMPLE!
WHAT?
YOU PUT THIS
HEAVY GARLAND ON
ME?
THAT GUY WENT
OUTSIDE.
PUT IT ON
HIM WHEN HE
RETURNS.
SIR,
WE BROUGHT THIS
FOR YOU.
WE'RE YOUR FANS!
FANS?
YES,
SIR.
WHAT?
YOU'RE OUR GOD!
WHAT'S THIS?
FANS?
WHAT ARE FANS
TO ME?
WAIT!
STILL,
WHAT ARE FANS
TO ME?
HEY,
SIR!
CHIRANJEEVI HAS FANS,
WILL ARAVIND HAVE
THEM?
VENKATESH HAS FANS,
WILL SURESH HAVE
THEM?
RAMA HAS DEVOTEES,
WILL HANUMAN HAVE
THEM?
OH,
I GUESS SO.
MEANING,
SIR,
THE REASON BOY
BECAME SO GREAT
TODAY,
ISN'T IT YOUR
BRAIN?
PEOPLE MIGHT NOT
KNOW WHAT HAPPENED,
BUT WE KNOW,
SIR.
NEVER MIND.
AT LEAST YOU
RECOGNIZED IT.
THAT'S WHY,
SIR,
WE BECAME FANS
OF YOUR FACE.
WE BECAME SLAVES
TO YOUR BRAIN.
LIKE YOUR BRAIN,
WE ALSO USED
OUR BRAIN AND
STARTED SMALL VENTURES.
JUST LIKE THEY
GIVE SHARES TO
TIRUPATI GOD FROM
PROFITS,
WE WILL GIVE
THEM TO YOU.
IN THE FIRST
VENTURE,
WE SAVED 1
MILLION.
HERE'S YOUR 10%.